Wheeler Blackwell Papers
Wheeler Blackwell Papers
1852-1889
Blackwell, Wheeler.
1.5 linear ft.
Wheeler Blackwell was a jeweler from Lodi, New York. Collection contains correspondence, memorabilia, printed material, and postcards.
2728907
Biographical History
Internal evidence of the collection suggests that Wheeler Blackwell was a jeweler in Lodi, New York in the late 19th century.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Wheeler Blackwell Papers consists of correspondence, memorabilia, printed material, and postcards.
Arrangement of the Collection
Material is in chronological order within series.
Subject and Genre Headings
New York State; Blackwell, Wheeler.; Jewelers -- New York (State); Business enterprises -- New York (State) -- History.; Lodi (N.Y.) -- Commerce.; Lodi (N.Y.) -- History.; Circulars (fliers); Correspondence.; Postcards.; Jewelers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Gift, 1980-1981.
Inventory
- Correspondence
  - Personal, 1852-1886; undated; 5 folders (Box 1)
  - Business, 1881-1889 (Box 1)
- Memorabilia
  - Miscellaneous, 1876-1880; undated (Box 1)
- Printed material
  - Advertising circulars, general, 1875-1883; undated (Box 1)
  - Advertising circulars, watches and clocks, 1880-1885; undated (Box 1)
- Postcards
  - Miscellaneous, 1875-1886; undated (Box 1)